Marvin C. Griffin papers, Inclusive: 1940-2011, undated, Bulk: 1960-1999, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Ministry, 1941-2011, undated; 1
  - Personal, 1956-2011, undated; 1
    - Personal Planner (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Personal Planner (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Personal Planner, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Personal Planner, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Personal Planner, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Personal Planner, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Personal Planner, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church, Financial (1 of 2), 1993-2011 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church, Financial (2 of 2), 1993-2011 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church-30th Pastoral Anniversary Celebration, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Church Contact Information, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - State Congress of Christian Workers, 1990-1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Case Study of Church Service, circa 1956 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - “African American Women in the Black Baptist Church” by Marvin C. Griffin, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - “Relational Prayer Witnessing” by Howard A. Tryon, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - “Families in Crises: Horses Without Riders” by Florence and Brannan Temple, 2003-204 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - “A Tribute to Our Pastor” by Congregants of Ebenezer Baptist Church, 1981 July 12 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - “MLK-A Drum Major for All Seasons” by Lawrence E. Carter, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas-Theological Education Study Committee Minutes, 1994 July 25-26 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - National Baptists, 1941-2009, undated; 2
    - “A History of the National Baptist Convention of America” by Marvin C. Griffin (1 of 2), 1986 June (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - “A History of the National Baptist Convention of America” by Marvin C. Griffin (2 of 2), 1986 June (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - “History and Compendium of the National Baptist Convention of America, 1880-1980” by Rhoda J. Hutch, 1983 June (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Sunday School Pamphlets, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Guide: Supervised Practice of Ministry Program: Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches—Christian Education Enrichment Program (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches—Christian Education Enrichment Program (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches—Christian Education Enrichment Program (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches—Christian Education Enrichment Program, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches—Christian Education Enrichment Program, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - National Missionary Baptist Fellowship of Churches Winter Session Conference, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Missionary Baptist General Convention Constitution, 1956-1966 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Missionary Baptist General Convention of Texas Statistician’s Report by Marvin C. Griffin, 1966-2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Missionary Baptist General Convention of Texas Session Programs, 1958-2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary-Supervised Practice of Ministry, 1988-1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - National Baptist Sunday School and Training Union Congress, 1973 June 12-17 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Copies of Old Convention Minutes, 1882-1900 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Copy of Charter for Baptist Missionary Educational Convention, The State of Texas, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Baptist Association Notes, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - “Keep Telling the Story” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Sunday School and Training Union Congress, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - “Teaching Christ Through the Black Experience” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Sunday School and Training Union Congress, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - “Teaching Techniques for Outreach” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Sunday School and Training Union Congress, 1979 June 15 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - “In Pursuit of Maturity” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Sunday School and Training Union Congress, 1989 June 13 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - “From Egypt to Canaan” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Convention, 2001 September (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - “Historian’s Report” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Convention and National Congress, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - “Toiling Through Tears” by Marvin C. Griffin at Missionary Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1962 October 24 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - “The Foreign Mission Board” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Convention, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - “Pattern for Church Growth” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers, 1998 June 24 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers-Correspondence, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers-Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers-Annual Programs and Reports (1 of 2), 1989-2002 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers-Annual Programs and Reports (2 of 2), 1989-2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers Annual Session, 2001 June 18-22 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers Annual Session, 2002 June 17-21 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - National Baptist Congress of Christian Workers Annual Session Evaluations, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Women’s Auxiliary Meeting Program, 1950 September 6-10 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Programs, 1985-1995 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Reports (1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Reports (2 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Cabinet Meeting, 1998 November 23-24 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Programs, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Programs, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Programs, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - National Baptist Convention of America-Foreign Mission Board Report, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Journals and Programs, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Mid-Winter Board Meeting, 2002 February 25-March 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Constitution, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - National Baptist Convention of America Inc., Sunday School and Training Union Congress-Class on Peace and Justice Issues, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - National Baptist Sunday School and Baptist Training Union Congress-Teacher Training Department, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - “Historian’s Report-Convention Involvement in Governmental Affairs” by Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Programs, 1980-1989 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Programs, 1993-2010 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Correspondence, 1977-1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Annual Session Minutes, 1999 July 19-26 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Annual Session, 2000 July 17-24 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - St. John Regular Baptist Association Financial Report, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Baptist Joint Committee Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Baptist Joint Committee Correspondence, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Baptist Joint Committee Board Meeting, 1999 October 4-5 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Baptist Joint Committee Reports, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - “Apology for Slavery” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Convention of America Inc., undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Social Justice Commission Report, National Baptist Convention of America Inc., 2001 September 5 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - “Health Care Issues of the 90s” by the Commission on Social Justice of the National Baptist Convention of America Inc., undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - “Historiographers-African Methodist Episcopal Church” by Dennis C. Dickerson, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - First Annual Session of the Minister’s Wives Conference of the National Baptist Convention of America, 1986 September 9 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - “Brothers in Black” by J. McDowell Richards at Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1941 December (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Official Journal of General Baptist Convention of Missouri, Kansas, and Nebraska, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Congress of National Black Churches, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - “Black Baptists Views Concerning Convention Structure” by Marvin C. Griffin at National Baptist Convention, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - “Black Baptists and Economic Empowerment” by Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Afro-American Baptists: A Guide to Materials in the American Baptist Historical Society, 1985 April (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Collected Programs (1 of 2), 1968-2000 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Collected Programs (2 of 2), 1968-2000 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Baptist History and Heritage, Vol. XIII, No. 3, 1978 July (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Baptist General Convention of Texas-African American Advisory Committee Meeting, 2002 March 26 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Report on Examination, Boards of the National Baptist Convention of America, 1961 June 30 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - National Baptist Publishing Board, 1965-1976 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - “The Immortality of Influence” by Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - “Worship Messages” by O.M. Locust at National Baptist Laymen’s Convention, 1951 September 5-7 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - “Implications of Multiple Affiliation for Black Southern Baptists” by Harold T. Branch, 1981 March 15 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - “Response to Dr. Harold T. Branch’s Paper ‘Implications of Multiple Affiliation for Black Southern Baptists’” by Marvin C. Griffin, 1981 April 22 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Yearbook: Baptist World Alliance, 1991 July 7-14 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Yearbook: Baptist World Alliance, 1992 July 4-12 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Yearbook: Baptist World Alliance, 1993 August 4-10 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Yearbook: Baptist World Alliance, 1994 July 20-23 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Civic Engagement, 1955-2006, undated; 2
  General condition: Good.
  The Civic Engagement series includes records and administrative files for various political and civic organizations of which Marvin C. Griffin was an active member. The series is in good condition.
  - Report of Austin Child Care Council, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Austin School Board, Financial, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - School Board Affairs: Austin (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - School Board Affairs: Austin (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - School Board Affairs: Austin (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Austin Schools (1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Austin Schools (2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Austin Schools (3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Austin Tri-Ethnic Community Council (1 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Austin Tri-Ethnic Community Council (2 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Austin Tri-Ethnic Community Council (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Austin Tri-Ethnic Community Council (4 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Austin Community College: Employment of Minorities, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Austin Independent School District Desegregation Suit (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Austin Independent School District Desegregation Suit (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - President’s Manual-Young Men’s Christian Association, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Model City Agency: Waco, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Population Growth, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Progressive Voter’s League (1 of 4), 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Progressive Voter’s League (2 of 4), 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Progressive Voter’s League (3 of 4), 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Progressive Voter’s League (4 of 4), 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Education Administration: Marvin C. Griffin, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - National Congress for Community Economic Development, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Urban Strategy Council, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Waco Parks and Recreation Commission Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - City Council Campaign, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - “The Black Family” Notes, 1992-1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Regarding Desegregation at Anderson High School, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - East Austin Economic Development Corporation, 1996-2003 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Rebuild America Program, 2000 February (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Black Advisory Committee Meeting Report, 1984 March 20-22 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Austin Downtown Lions Financial Statement, 2004 January 18 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Austin Area Research Organization Inc., 2006 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - One Star Foundation, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Religious Institutions as Partners in Community Based Development: Project Achievements Survey, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Thank You Letters from Pleasant Hill School, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Zone Legislation, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Religious Freedom Restoration Act, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Reserving and Renting Space in Austin, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Subject Files, 1943-2011, undated; 3
  The Subject Files series includes Marvin C. Griffin's research for all areas of his career, sorted by organization or topic. There is also some biographical material on the Griffin family. The series is in good condition.
  - Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary-Project Proposal, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Austin Presbyterian Theological Seminary Correspondence, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Bishop College: Institute Messages, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Bishop College: Institute Messages, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Bishop College: Institute Messages, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Bishop College: L.K. Williams Ministers’ Institute: “Reflections:, 1964 April 28-May1 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Bishop College: L.K. Williams Ministers’ Institute: “The Christian Ministry in an Emerging Age of Space, 1962 May 1-4 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Ecumenical Institute: Chicago: “Songs of the Spirit Movement”, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Business Cards: Marvin C. Griffin: Ebenezer Baptist Church, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Austin American-Statesman: “Angels of Change”: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2007 September 23 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Campus Visits, 1989-1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Governor Ann Richards Correspondence, 1992 May 1 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Church Funding Resource Guide, 1992 July (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Europe Trip, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Negro Baptists in America, 1959-1964 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Christian Sexuality, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - “Flames from the Altar” by Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - “Environmental Control for the Allergic Patient”, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - “Black Baptists Beginnings” by Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - “Boardwalk Empire” Teleplay, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence Edward Carter, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Ministers Association of Killeen and Copperas Cove Area Summer Institute, 1985 May 6-10 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Planning, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Correspondence, 1974-2010, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Crawford Martin and Waggoner Carr, 1965-1966 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Black Ministries (1 of 4), 1968-1972 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Black Ministries (2 of 4), 1968-1972 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Black Ministries (3 of 4), 1968-1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Black Ministries (4 of 4), 1968-1972 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - History of the Black Church, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Internship: Malartha Bosier: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Religious Journalism: Marvin C. Griffin, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Religious Psychology: Marvin C. Griffin, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Reports, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rodney Ellis Packet of Appreciation, 1945-2002 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Ebenezer Extra: Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2003 February (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Bishop College: “Impact: Bishop College and Government”, 1977 September 30 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Dispute Resolution Center, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church: Offerings, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church: Offerings, 1970 January-May (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church: Offerings, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Certificates: Ordination and Appreciation, 1940-2007 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Diploma: Bachelor of Divinity: Marvin C. Griffin, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Diploma: Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary: Master of Religious Education: Marvin C. Griffin, 1955 May 13 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Pins: Politics: Black Caucus: Family Service Association of America, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Proclamations and Resolutions, 1986-1990, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Convention Ribbons, 1971-1998 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Photobook: 42nd Pastoral Anniversary and Retirement Celebration, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Sheila Jackson Lee, House of Representatives, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Visual Aids (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Visual Aids (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Worship, 1969-1972 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Summer School on the Church and Evangelism, 1959 July 6-24 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - The Christian Ministry, 1969-1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - “A Theological Rationale for the Ebenezer Baptist Church Worship Experience” by Marvin C. Griffin, 1987 June (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Current Events Bible Study, 2005 September 1 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Academy of Millinery Design (1 of 3), undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Academy of Millinery Design (2 of 3), undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Academy of Millinery Design (3 of 3), undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Clarity of Pastor’s Call, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Types of Christian Apologetics, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Summer School on the Church and the Urban Ministry, 1958 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Parish Ministers’ Colloquy-Christian Faith and Life Community, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Book Reviews, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Political Correspondence, 1962-2011 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Martin Luther King Messages, 1970-1987 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, General, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Africa, 1965-1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - West Africa Study Tour, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Bishop College (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Bishop College (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - General Epistles, Dr. Craig, circa 1945 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Church Calendar, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Mary Allen College, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Church Administration, 1959-1962 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Ministers Conference-General Baptist Convention, 1954-1962 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Christian Education, circa 1950 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Union Baptist District Congress (1 of 2), 1954-1965 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Union Baptist District Congress (2 of 2), 1954-1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - General Baptist Convention, 1953-1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Letter to Laymen, 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy and Science (1 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Philosophy and Science (2 of 2), 1965-1968 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - “Foundations for Responsible Twentieth Century Preaching” by John Malcus Ellison, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Mary Allen College Board of Trustees, 1954-1962 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Mary Allen College Board of Trustees, 1962-1967 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Air Conditioning, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Philosophy of Christianity, Dr. Horton, 1945 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Organization Charters and By-Laws, 1947-1963 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - S.A. Pleasant Ministers Institute (1 of 2), 1952-1961 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - S.A. Pleasant Ministers Institute (2 of 2), 1952-1961 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Collected Church Bulletins (1 of 2), 1952-1962 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Collected Church Bulletins (2 of 2), 1952-1962 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Essays from Seminary Courses [RESTRICTED], 1955 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Political Clippings, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Preaching Roles and Techniques, circa 1948 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Personal Creed, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Homolitics and Religious Biographies, circa 1945 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Civic Matters, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Texas Council of Negro Voters, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee of Waco, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Church Music, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - United Political Organization Memberships, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Church and Race, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Psychology and Dealing with People, Dr. Bell [RESTRICTED], circa 1955 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (1 of 2), 1950-1963 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (2 of 2), 1950-1963 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Theology, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - City of Waco-Progressive Voter’s League, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Ways of Salvation, Dr. Hamilton [RESTRICTED], 1945 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Pastor’s Conference, San Antonio, 1968 September 3 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Marvin C. Griffin Personal Publicity, circa 1962 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Texas Southern University-Manpower Development and Training Program, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - “Some Implications in the Recent Decisions of the Supreme Court Effecting Race Relations” by A.C. Miller, undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Personal Letters, 1953-1990 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Women’s Missionary Union, 1950-1955 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Political Action-Progressive Voter’s League (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Political Action-Progressive Voter’s League (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Progressive Voter’s League, 1958-1964 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - New Hope Baptist Church Workshop of Christian Stewardship, circa 1952 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - ABO Investors (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - ABO Investors (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - “The Black Church in America”, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - “The Bible and Justice”, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Baptist World Alliance, 1955-1970 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Computer, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Speeches, 1965-1985 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - “Covenant and Liberation in Salvation History” by Marvin C. Griffin, 1990 April (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Shiloh Baptist Correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Calls to Worship, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Deacon Wives and Deaconesses, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Dog-Certified Pedigree, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Dedication Services, 1953-1966 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Congress of Christian Workers Session at Ebenezer Baptist Church, 1964 August 18-24 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Illustrations, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Lenten Messages on Last Seven Words, 1962-1999 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. Griffin Knitshop Correspondence, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Lois Griffin [RESTRICTED], 1970-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Meditations, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)